hotimportnights.com 2009-11-01

# Hot Import Nights - car shows, car models, music and lifestyle events

This privacy statement covers the site HINcity.com and hotimportnights.com furthermore collectively referred to as HIN.

**Information Collection**

**Registration**  
In order to use certain parts of this Web site, a user must first complete a registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which (s)he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide other unique identifiers (such as first and last name), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. 

**User Profile**  
User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate member interactions in HIN. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join HIN, to attach “Member Friends”, and to send notifications related to the service.

**Profile**  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that detail their user information and preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the user’s personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user's visit to our Web site and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. Your profile is shared in aggregate form only. No personally identifiable information is shared with any 3rd party. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time.   
By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user may not be able to view areas of the site requiring user login. 

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Communications from the Site**

**Special Offers and Updates**  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice/Opt-out section. 

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

**Sharing**

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. Personally Identifiable Information collected by HIN may also be used for other purposes including but not limited to site administration and troubleshooting. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service and our newsletter provider, for example) may access such information.

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**  
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

**Business Transitions**  
In the event HIN goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by via an opt-out checkbox on the member profile page.   
Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Through features available on our site, third parties may use cookies or other technology to gather information. HIN does not control the use of this technology or the resulting information and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, HIN, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. 

**Message Boards, Public Forums, Chat Rooms and Classifieds**  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, on a classified ad or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

**Security**  
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. 

**Children**  
HIN does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe HIN has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us.

**Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (information asked during registration), we provide a way to correct or update users' personally identifiable information. This can be done at the member profile page. 

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
